DAQUAN (ALEXANDRA) WU

35 River Drive South, Jersey City, NJ 07310 + daguanwu777@gmail.com + 518.698.2545

QUALIFICATIONS PROFILE

Emerging financial professional equipped with graduate-level academic credentials and hands-on management experience poised to contribute solid mathematic, statistical analysis, and communication skills in a challenging position in Business/Finance area. Trained and practiced in advanced quantitative financial and economic computational methodologies with focused attention to detail for performing complex tasks. Dynamic team leader and contributor exhibiting strengths in researching, assembling, organizing, and manipulating financial data. Proficient with Mac and Windows operating system, Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint), SPSS, eViews, MATLAB, R, and Visual Basic (VB).Native Chinese and fluent English language skills.

EDUCATION & PROFESSIONAL ASSOCIATIONS

MS, Finance Engineering and Risk Analytics (2013) – RENSSELAER POLYTECHNIC INSTITUTE, Lally School of Management and Technology, Troy, NY

Selected Projects: Evaluated and prepared a study on early introduction of the new iPhone 5.~ Generated quantitative estimates of economic policy uncertainty on asset prices in the U.S. and in China.~ Contributed to development of an investment strategy for hedging British pound futures exchange rate risk.~ Participated in a simulation project focused on creating a tracking index to replicate the S&P 500.~ Generated and identified optimal regression model while investigating economic challenges associated with the use of housing market data to measure willingness to pay for clean air.

BS, Business Administration, concentration Entrepreneurship and Economics, minor Mathematics (2011)

- SAINT LOUIS UNIVERSITY, St. Louis, MO

Graduated Magna cum Laude ~ Achieved 3.7/4.0 GPA ~ Entrepreneurial CEO & SLU Economic Clubs

Professional Affiliations & Honor Societies

Global Association of Risk Professionals (GARP), *Since 2012* ~ Omicron Delta Epsilon, International Economics Honor Society, *Since 2011* ~ Omicron Delta Kappa, National Leadership Honor Society, *Since 2010* ~ Golden Key, International Honor Society, *Since 2010*

EXPERIENCE HIGHLIGHTS

POINT GLOBAL L.L.C, New York, NY

Hedge Fund Marketing Internship, 02/2014 - Present

Performed several tasks centered on hedge fund research and due diligence. Identified potential strategic partners with certain specific geographic locations and establish initial contracts for more than 1500 companies.

ENTRINSICO, Seattle, Washington

International Financial Consultant Internship, 02/2014 - 04/2014

Provided assistance in preparation of financial forecast section in the company's internal business plan. Coordinated and supported to the top finance management team. Researched and analyzed competitive environment, organized and managed all financial data.

SHAOXING JINHAOSHENG IMPORT & EXPORT LIMITED, Zhejiang, China

Assistant General Manager, 12/2011 - 6/2012

Played integral role in growing business and achieving annualized profits of \$250K+ while managing day-to-day import/export and financial operations. Calculated and ensured timely relay of accurate information. Maintained and shared up-to-date knowledge of trading laws, tax regulations, and competitive market pricing.